let questions = [
  {
    num: 1,
    question:
      "Who was the first baseball player to be featured on a U.S. postage stamp?",
    answer: "C: Jackie Robinson",
    score: 500,
    dieScore: 350,
    options: [
      "A: Roberto Clemente",
      "B: Lou Gehrig",
      "C: Jackie Robinson",
      "D: Babe Ruth",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 2,
    question:
      "When three celestial bodies form a straight line, what is it called?",
    answer: "B: Syzygy",
    score: 500,
    dieScore: 350,
    options: ["A: Simoom", "B: Syzygy", "C: String theory", "D: Saprobity"],
  },
  {
    num: 3,
    question:
      "“Satisfaction guaranteed or your money back” was first advertised in the 1870s by what company?",
    answer: "C: Montgomery Ward",
    score: 500,
    dieScore: 350,
    options: ["A: JCPenny", "B: Sears", "C: Montgomery Ward", "D: Macy's"],
  },
  {
    num: 4,
    question:
      "Six U.S. presidents had what first name, the most common presidential name in history?",
    answer: "C: James",
    score: 1000,
    dieScore: 1000,
    options: ["A: John", "B: William", "C: James", "D: George"],
  },
  {
    num: 5,
    question:
      "A person who suffers from coulrophobia has an intense fear of what?",
    answer: "D: Clowns",
    score: 2500,
    dieScore: 2000,
    options: ["A: Cemeteries", "B: Needles", "C: Tunnels", "D: Clowns"],
  },
  {
    num: 6,
    question: "What is Bart Simpson's middle name?",
    answer: "C: JoJo",
    score: 5000,
    dieScore: 3000,
    options: ["A: Juniper", "B: Jebediah", "C: JoJo", "D: Jacqueline"],
  },
  {
    num: 7,
    question:
      "In 1974, which celebrity appeared on the first cover of People magazine?",
    answer: "D: Mia Farrow",
    score: 5000,
    dieScore: 3000,
    options: [
      "A: Elizabeth Taylor",
      "B: Jane Fonda",
      "C: Mary Taylor Moore",
      "D: Mia Farrow",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 8,
    question:
      "How many children did Captain Von Trapp have in the musical The Sound of Music?",
    answer: "A: Seven",
    score: 5000,
    dieScore: 3000,
    options: ["A: Seven", "B: Eight", "C: Six", "D: Nine"],
  },
  {
    num: 9,
    question: "The computer language Ada is named for what poet's daughter?",
    answer: "A: Lord Byron",
    score: 10000,
    dieScore: 8000,
    options: [
      "A: Lord Byron",
      "B: Walt Whitman",
      "C: T.S. Eliot",
      "D: Emily Dickinson",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 10,
    question:
      "Of the fifteen tallest buildings in the world, more than half are in what country?",
    answer: "B: China",
    score: 10000,
    dieScore: 8000,
    options: [
      "A: Saudi Arabia",
      "B: China",
      "C: United Arab Emirates",
      "D: Malaysia",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 11,
    question:
      "A gangster cliche for going to jail, the phrase up the river originally referred to a prison up what river?",
    answer: "B: Hudson River",
    score: 10000,
    dieScore: 8000,
    options: [
      "A: Ohio River",
      "B: Hudson River",
      "C: St. Lawrence River",
      "D: Rio Grande",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 12,
    question:
      "In the 120-count box of Crayola crayons, which of the following is not the name of a crayon color?",
    answer: "D: Gray matter",
    score: 50000,
    dieScore: 40000,
    options: [
      "A: Fuzzy wuzzy brown",
      "B: Mauvelous",
      "C: Asparagus",
      "D: Gray matter",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 13,
    question:
      "Now used primarily by the blind, Braille writing was derived from a system originally used by whom?",
    answer: "C: Soldiers",
    score: 50000,
    dieScore: 40000,
    options: ["A: Farmers", "B: Accountants", "C: Soldiers", "D: Prisoners"],
  },
  {
    num: 14,
    question:
      "Which of these compounds in the human body is classified by scientists as a steroid?",
    answer: "B: Cholesterol",
    score: 100000,
    dieScore: 75000,
    options: ["A: Hemoglobin", "B: Cholesterol", "C: Insulin", "D: Glucose"],
  },
  {
    num: 15,
    question:
      "In Caracas, Venezuela, it is customary on the mornings leading up to Christmas for people to travel to church on what?",
    answer: "A: Roller skates",
    score: 250000,
    dieScore: 150000,
    options: [
      "A: Roller skates",
      "B: Water buffaloes",
      "C: Ostriches",
      "D: Ziplines",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 16,
    question:
      "Of the fifteen tallest buildings in the world, more than half are in what country?",
    answer: "B: China",
    score: 500000,
    dieScore: 500000,
    options: [
      "A: Saudi Arabia",
      "B: China",
      "C: United Arab Emirates",
      "D: Malaysia",
    ],
  },
];
